[
    {
        "question": "Why is AWS more economical than traditional data centers for applications with varying compute workloads?",
        "answer": "Amazon EC2 instances can be launched on-demand when needed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which AWS service would simplify migration of a database to AWS?",
        "answer": "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which AWS offering enables customers to find, buy, and immediately start using software solutions in their AWS environment?",
        "answer": "AWS Marketplace"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which AWS networking service enables a company to create a virtual network within AWS?",
        "answer": "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is AWS's responsibility under the AWS shared responsibility model?",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "Configuring third-party applications"
            },
            {
                "option": "Maintaining physical hardware"
            },
            {
                "option": "Securing application access and data"
            },
            {
                "option": "Managing custom Amazon Machine Images (AMIs)"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "Maintaining physical hardware"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which component of AWS global infrastructure does Amazon CloudFront use to ensure low-latency delivery?",
        "answer": "AWS edge locations"
    },
    {
        "question": "How would a system administrator add an additional layer of login security to a user's AWS Management Console?",
        "answer": "Enable Multi-Factor Authentication"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which service can identify the user that made the API call when an Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instance is terminated?",
        "answer": "AWS CloudTrail"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which service would you use to send alerts based on Amazon CloudWatch alarms?",
        "answer": "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can a customer find information aboutprohibited actions onAWS infrastructure?",
        "answer": "AWS Acceptable Use Policy"
    }
]